Until October 7, you and other Israelis helped drive people from Gaza to hospitals in Israel. Will you work for dialogue and cooperation again?
It's useless,
It's not doing anything.
And there is a war now,
and it's a right war, I'm sorry to say.
But it's a right war.
There's no other way.
It's hard,
I'm crying a lot about it,
but it has to be.
The IDF is doing what they have to do now.
I hope when... and it will finish soon,
we will call and see if we'll be back.
We will start over to talk about
not about peace, about life.
And I don't think that
Derech Hachlama (medical transport charity)
will be helpful.
They have to do it in their own country.
Someone else has to do it.
We failed, we failed.
My generation failed to make a safe place.
Know the reason.
New generations and new leaders have to grow up
and take us to good places.